System requirements UvA_EEG_recorder

The UvA_EEG_recorder has been developed in MATLAB R2015a, and succesfully tested in later versions up until R2017b. The recorder has been designed to record 8 analog EEG channels and 6 optional digital channels from a g.MOBIlab+ DAC device by g.tec (Guger Technologies)

N.B.! The functionality of the data analysis tools of UvA_EEG_recorder has fewer requirements than the recording functionality, and is thus functional on a wider range of systems. The requirements are listed separately for recording use and analysis use.

Requirements for RECORDING purposes:
	- Windows 7 or higher (Because the MOBIlab-MATLAB API is 	only available for windows. Additionally there is no 	MATLAB Data Acquisition Toolbox vailable for MAC OS)

	- MATLAB:
		* R2014 / R2015
		* 32-bit version. (R2015 is the most recent MATLAB 			version still available in 32-bit, later versions 			are 	only available in 64-bit.)
		* MATLAB Data Acquisition Toolbox

	For use with g.tec's MOBIlab+:
		* g.MOBIlab driver
		* Gtec MOBIlab API 32 bit API
		When using the Bluetooth dongle:
		* 64 bit driver for Bluetooth 
		* 32 bit driver for Bluetooth
		When using a data cable:
		* ATEN UC232A driver 


Requirements for DATA ANALYSIS purposes:
	- Windows 7 or higher / MAC OS .. or higher
	- LINUX: Not tested
	- MATLAB:
		* R2014 or higher
		* 32-bit or 64-bit version
		* Signal Processing Toolbox


  
